What was that?
An explosion?
We are the People's Eastern Revolution Front.
We have assumed control of this train.
I repeat, we are the People's Eastern Revolution Front.
Sounds like a bunch of names cut and pasted together.
I certainly haven't heard of it.
I'll bet it's another new radical group.
Jeez, what is this world coming to?
Aren't you going to do something?
Why do I have to?
I mean, you can take those guys
all by yourself, right, Major?
Indeed!
As if they could hijack a train with the Strong Arm Alchemist
Alex Louis Armstrong on board!
Come here, you crooks!
You shall regret your bad luck, I assure you!
All right, you!
What?
Who are you, freaks?
You heard the announcement, didn't you?
This train's now under the control
of the Eastern Liberation Federation.
I guess they've changed their names since the announcement.
I just can't take this anymore.
Hey, wait. Weren't we just in a situation like this?
Yeah, we were.
Someone must have put a curse on us.
Hey, you and the armor man, Shorty!
Who gave you permission to chat?
Just shut up and fork over the valuables!
This is perfect.
Okay, you take the goods from the
muffler man and the armor.
Then get your butt over here, Shorty!
Who are you calling Shorty?!
Ha! You, of course!
Who the heck else is there, you Shorty?
Who are you calling a runt so tiny
he could only be seen with a magnifying glass?!
Impressive, Edward Elric.
An alchemist?
That was pitiful.
Just who are these people anyway?
I'm telling you, it's a curse.
Or maybe they want your autograph.
What? Who?
Hey, what's going on in here?
Maybe he's a fan of yours.
Very funny.
All right, Major.
You go check out the cars in the back
and find out what that explosion was.
Don't worry about it. I'm already on it.
Looks like we've got alchemists among us.
So everybody watch your backs, okay?
Hmm, I know it all too well.
Let's go!