Are you okay, brother?
Yeah. But still, there are just too many of them...
That's true.
Seems like you're having trouble, Fullmetal!
Battle requires efficiency.
If you face an enemy overwhelming you with numbers one-on-one,
you’ll eventually wear yourself out and collapse.
Colonel.
And battle also requires beauty!
Lord Armstrong.
Beautiful physiques hold beautiful techniques;
beautiful techniques hold beautiful power!
Behold, the artistic alchemy passed down through generations of the Armstrong family!
Enough with the boring lecture.
Just get to the point, please!
Wait, hold on a second.
Did you already... figure it out?
We have a problem, Edward. Armony has been kidnapped!
What?! Armony? By whom?
Greta, the assistant. She’s probably still inside the castle.
Leave this to us. Go after her!
She's surely waiting for you!
Brother...
Yeah...
Damn it!