Where's Armony?
...
Thank you.
Hold it right there.
Hey, if you can't tell, we're in a hurry.
The report will have to wait.
Hold it, I said.
What's gotten into you?
I was specifically asked not to allow your entry.
By who?
Is that so?
Well, then we're just gonna have
to force ourselves in.
I'm sorry to do this,
but we're not gonna hold back.
Edward, you have to listen to us.
There's no time. Armony's in danger.
You never stop to think, do you?
Think about Armony's feelings.
Armony's feelings?
Who cares?
She's my...
My apprentice.
I have to help.
I have to save her.
What good is a master
who can't help his apprentice?
What good is alchemy then?
So you have to.
Yes, I have to.
Then you give me no choice.
You think we're only kids, don't you?
And we'll grow up soon enough.
But that's not true for Armony.
Now is all she has!
I figured this day would come around sometime.
Get out of the way!