You've got to be kidding.
That's impossible.
You weren't able to transmute a single thing.
Is this the end?
Is this it?
Armony!
Could I be so helpless?
Why couldn't I do anything?
Why am I so powerless?
Ed, look.
What is that?
A feather?
Armony's?
So it is.
Does it hurt?
Hi, Daddy.
You must hate me by now, but...
That's silly. How could I hate you?
You don't have to talk anymore.
My dear, you may not have realized this,
but I have always loved you.
I cared for you more than
anyone else ever could.
But no matter what I tried,
I just couldn't understand
what would make you the happiest.
What I could do to make
my daughter happy.
Daddy, you're so silly.
I knew. I always knew.
Because I'm your daughter,
and daughters always know.
Daddy, I...
Yes, dear?
I am your daughter, aren't I?
Silly girl, of course you are.
Okay. I guess we're both silly then.
Like father, like daughter.
Armony!
Don't be afraid.
I won't let you go alone.
This will be ours...
I'm sorry.
And... I...
You dummy. You big dummy.
Are you satisfied?
Does that make you happy?
Did you see?
Were they smiling, Edward?